{
    "subject": "resource/Andriy_Hlushchenko",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Andriy Hlushchenko (born 18 March 1974) is a Ukrainian football goalkeeper coach at Chornomorets Odessa of the Ukrainian Premier League. Prior to that, he played at Torpedo Zaporizhia, Zirka Kirovohrad, Metalurh Zaporizhya, llychivets Mariupol and Chornomorets Odessa and was also a goalkeeper coach at Metalurh Zaporizhya.Andriy announced his retirement as a professional goalkeeper in the spring of 2009.",
    "human_readable": "Andriy Hlushchenko's comment is that he is a Ukrainian football goalkeeper coach at Chornomorets Odessa of the Ukrainian Premier League, and prior to that, he played at several teams, retiring from professional play in the spring of 2009.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.928398847579956,
            "question": "For which Ukrainian football team does Andriy Hlushchenko currently work as a coach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9199954867362976,
            "question": "Is Andriy Hlushchenko currently involved in the Ukrainian football scene?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8980797529220581,
            "question": "Did Andriy Hlushchenko play professionally before becoming a coach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8853883147239685,
            "question": "When did Andriy Hlushchenko retire from professional football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8847256898880005,
            "question": "What year did Andriy Hlushchenko retire from professional football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8541234135627747,
            "question": "What is Andriy Hlushchenko's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8399362564086914,
            "question": "What position did Andriy Hlushchenko play during his professional career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8336458206176758,
            "question": "Besides Chornomorets Odessa, for what other teams did Andriy Hlushchenko play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7122493982315063,
            "question": "In what league does Chornomorets Odessa play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6376429200172424,
            "question": "What is the name of the league where Chornomorets Odessa competes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andriy Hlushchenko's comment is that he is a Ukrainian football goalkeeper coach at Chornomorets Odessa of the Ukrainian Premier League, and prior to that, he played at several teams, retiring from professional play in the spring of 2009.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1578_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what league does Chornomorets Odessa play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1578_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides Chornomorets Odessa, for what other teams did Andriy Hlushchenko play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1578_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position did Andriy Hlushchenko play during his professional career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1578_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1578_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents support all aspects of the query about Andriy Hlushchenko. They confirm his role as a Ukrainian football goalkeeper coach, his prior teams (Torpedo Zaporizhia, Zirka Kirovohrad, Metalurh Zaporizhya, llychivets Mariupol, and Chornomorets Odessa), and that he retired from professional play in the spring of 2009."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}